A Guide to the Papers of Carl Caskey Speidel 1923-1964
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- Label: A3b "Effects on Density duplicate," First Title: "Effects on density and cleavage of gamete irradiation in Arabacia," 400 feet of film ND (Box-folder 08:04)
- Label: A5 "Arabacia 5," First Title: "Radioresistance of Arabacia zygotes at different stages," 400 feet of film ND (Box-folder 08:05)
- Label: A6 "Arabacia 6," First Title: "Deviations in motility of irradiated sea urchins," 400 feet of film ND (Box-folder 08:06)
- Label: A7 "Arabacia 7 x-ray comparative," First Title: "Changes in 5 hours after x-irradiation zygotes 120 kr," 350 feet of film ND (Box-folder 08:07)
- Label: A8 "Arabacia 8, x-ray normal fert. and cleavage," First Title: "Multiple cleavage 4 hrs. after 128 kr. to sperm," 380 feet of film ND (Box-folder 08:08)
- Label: A10 "Arabacia UV to sperm only," First Title: "2 days after fertilization 15 s UV to sperm only," 300 feet of film ND (Box-folder 08:09)
- Label: A12 "Arabacia 12 caffeine," First Title: "6 hour cleavage after 1 hour M/10 caffeine to sperm," 320 feet of film ND (Box-folder 08:10)
- Label: A14 "Reel 14, Trichloroacetic acid Arabacia," First Title: "Trichloroacetic acid effects on gametes and zygotes of Arabacia," 100 feet of film ND (Box-folder 08:11)
- Label: Sigma Xi 1 "General Tissues, Sigma Xi," First Title: "Cine-photomicrographic studies of tadpole cells in vivo,"430 feet of film ND (Box-folder 08:12)
- Label: Sigma Xi 2 "Sigma Xi 2, Nerve growth, NIH," First Title: "Living cells in action," 420 feet of film ND (Box-folder 08:13)
- Label: Sigma Xi 3 "Extravasation of blood, reel 3 Sigma Xi," First Title: "Living cells in action," 420 feet of film ND (Box-folder 08:14)
- Label: "Bow X-rays," First Title: "Stages of recovery 18-48 hrs. after 400-700 kr," 250 feet of film ND (Box-folder 08:15)
- Label: "Black and white, New Orleans," First Title: "Reactions of cells in tadpoles to implanted substances," 300 feet of film ND (Box-folder 08:16)